漫威漫画
起来  检查房间
Up! Up! Up! Room check!
犯人  起立  面墙站好
Convict, stand and face the wall!
彻底搜查这里
Comb the area.
我们在对本区域进行强制搜查
We'll be conducting a mandatory sweep of the area.
你必须配合一切指示  明白吗
You're to cooperate with all instructions. You understand?
明白
I understand.
没问题
Check.
我在给你搜身  以确保你没有携带任何
I am searching your person to ensure you're not carrying anything
可能伤害你自己或他人的东西
that might be harmful to yourself or others.
明白吗
Do you understand?
明白
I understand.
没问题
Check.
转身
Turn around.
完事了吗
Are we finished here?
安全
All clear.
早上真是越来越冷了
Oh, these mornings are getting colder and colder.
这破玩意也不好用
Piece of crap can't keep up for nothing.
去哪  哥们
Where we off to, boss?
马特活着出现在我面前
Matt shows up alive,
却又告诉我再也别想见到他了
then tells me I'm never gonna see him again.
只有我  福吉·尼尔森能被一个鬼玩消失
Only I, Foggy Nelson, can be ghosted by a ghost.
锁好了  你都检查过好几次了
It's locked. Like it was the last time you checked it.
我们得再安装个固定栓
We need to get another dead bolt installed.
一个固定栓  一根弱锁链
A single dead bolt and a measly chain?
简直跟珠帘没什么区别
Might as well be a beaded curtain.
福吉  放松
Foggy, relax.
放松  你听到我的话了吗
Relax? Are you even listening to me?
威尔逊·菲斯克想宰了我
Wilson Fisk wants my scalp.
说不定  他还想杀你呢
And for all we know, he wants yours, too.
你反正也没帮过他
It's not like you've done him any favors.
当然了  马特要我靠边站
And of course Matt wants me to stick to the sidelines
他自己去对付菲斯克
while he deals with Fisk.
只有马特·默多克有资格去采取实际行动
Only Matt Murdock is fit for the real action.
-因为我不...  -什么
- Just because I'm not-- - What?
没什么
Nothing.
我都不知道我在说什么了
I don't even know what I'm saying anymore.
福吉  呼吸
Foggy, breathe.
马特本来不在了
Matt was gone.
现在他又回来了
Now he's back.
菲斯克放出来了
Fisk is out,
我不知道这下我是什么情况了
and I have no idea where that leaves me.
管他什么靠边站  我们要去进攻
Screw the sidelines. We go on the offense.
进攻  菲斯克吗
Offense? With Fisk?
他有法律和联调局给他站边
He has the law and the FBI on his side.
况且地检官也没说发话
And it's not like we've heard a statement from the DA
抨击他的释放
condemning his release.
不不  绝不能危及布雷克·陶瓦的再选
No, no, nothing to jeopardize Blake Tower's reelection.
他就不能有点种吗
God forbid he grow a pair.
这可以啊
Oh, that could work.
布雷克·陶瓦有种吗  不会的
Blake Tower growing a pair? Not gonna happen.
不  想想看
No, think about it.
想要保护你不被菲斯克伤害  最好的办法
The best way to protect yourself from Fisk
是制造声势  走到公众面前
is to make noise, is to be out in the open.
公开处刑吗
Oh, like a public execution.
是公开呼吁行动
Like a public call to action.
如果布雷克·陶瓦不肯去阻止菲斯克
If Blake Tower won't do anything to stop Fisk,
那就跟他竞选地检官
then run against him for district attorney.
如果你本就是目标了
If you're already a target,
那不如做第一个出拳的人
you might as well be the first person to take a swing.
我说真的
No, I'm serious.
你越受瞩目  危险就越小
The more public, the more you're protected.
我是不可能赢的
There's no way I can win.
-当然了  -谢谢你的信心
- Well, of course not. - Thank you for the confidence.
况且  我们早过了截止日期了
Anyways, we're light-years past the deadline.
那就作为未列名候选人参选
Then run as a write-in.
你就把你的参选资格建立在一个问题上
You base your candidacy on a single issue.
把菲斯克关回监狱
Putting Fisk back behind bars.
你也能拉到几票的
You'd bag a few votes.
虽然不足以胜利  但也能发声了
I mean, not enough to win, but you'd get the issue out there.
再说  还能赚到纽约警局的路人粉
Plus, you'd make a few friends in the NYPD, and...
这对于辩护律师来说可不算坏事
that's not the worst thing for a defense attorney.
你也可以继续检查门锁
Or you could keep checking the locks.
我不会让你有事的
I won't let anything happen to you.
宝贝
Oh, baby.
那我们得开始谋划那一拳了
Then we better start working on that swing.
先喝咖啡
After coffee.
你请客
You're buying.
你看到我的钱包了吗
Have you seen my wallet?
行了吗
This is good?
嗯  就这里
Yeah, here's fine.
你拿信用卡吗  现金更好
Hey, you paying with card? 'Cause, you know, cash is better.
等着我
Wait for me.
好  没问题
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I can do that.
早上好
Good morning.
-来访目的  -约了跟委托人见面
- Purpose for your visit? - I have an appointment with my client.
我打过电话  来访名单上该有我
I called earlier. I should be on the visitor list.
身份证件
ID.
我找不到钱包了
I can't find my wallet.
是留在家了吗  还是丢在出租车里了
Did I leave it at home, or drop it in the cab--
没有带照片身份证件  就不能...
Without picture ID, I can't--
稍等一下
Just give me one second.
先生  请让开等待...
Sir, please step aside while--
这是我的纽约律师编号
This is my New York Bar number.
虽然不带照片
Now, it's not picture ID, I know,
但是我花了七年时间
but it did take seven years
背负了30万学生贷款才拿到的
and cost me $300,000 in student loans.
能为我争取到什么吗
Does it, uh, buy me anything?
名字
Name?
尼尔森  富兰克林·尼尔森
Nelson. Franklin Nelson.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     夜魔草
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     知之
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
夜
魔
侠
第三季  第四集
-你好吗  -很好
- How you doin'? - Good.
还撑得住
You're holding up?
马特
Matt!
我以为福吉...
I thought Foggy...
-你好啊  迈克尔  -天呐
- What's up, Michael? - Oh, man.
-见到你太好了  -见到你我也很高兴
- It's good to see you. - It's good to see you, too.
-虽然是在这破地方  -你肯定在想...
- Even if it is in this shithole. - I'm sure you're wondering--
抱歉  我不该说破地方的
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said shithole.
我在努力不说脏话
I'm trying not to curse.
要不然等我18个月后出狱了
What's the point of me getting out of here in 18 months
还以最优异的成绩拿到了心理学学位
with a degree in psychology, top of my class...
却还满口脏话  那像他妈什么话
if I still swear like a goddamn sailor?
-又来了  -抱歉
- Did it again. - Well, sorry.
圣徒马修啊
Saint Matthew.
得了  我才不是圣徒
No, come on, I'm no saint.
你和福吉帮我减去了16年的刑期
You and Foggy got 16 years knocked off my sentence.
如果这不是神迹  那什么是
If that's not divine intervention, huh?
福吉呢  从没见过你俩不一起来
Where is Foggy? I've never seen you two apart.
我们已经不再合伙了
We're not, uh... We're not working together anymore.
-那真糟  -是啊
- Aw, man, that sucks. - Yeah.
我不希望有人
Listen, I don't want anyone,
包括福吉知道我来了...
even Foggy, to know that I was here, so...
没问题
Yeah, I can do that.
-多谢  -什么事啊
- Appreciate it. - So, what's the big mystery?
那个  你跟阿尔巴尼亚帮干过吧
Yeah, so, look, you, um... worked with the Albanians, right?
很久以前了
A long time ago.
也就低端的事  主要是运货
Low-level stuff. Mostly just running.
但他们会在这里保护你
But they're offering you protection in here?
你找阿尔巴尼亚帮干什么
What do you want with the Albanians?
我希望你介绍一下
I want an introduction.
如果有人需要辩护律师
If somebody needs a defense lawyer,
我一定会提你的名字
I'll make sure to pass your name along.
五星好评  但是
Glowing review. But, you know,
这里的人  都是杀人混蛋
folks in here, they're murdering bastards.
我想认识维克·尤瑟菲
I want an introduction to Vic Jusufi.
没人能接触维克
Nobody gets in with Vic.
你办不到吗
You can't make it happen?
...多加的两年刑期
...and the extra two years added?
你找他干什么啊
What do you want with him, anyway?
威尔逊·菲斯克本可以告任何犯罪集团的密
Wilson Fisk could've turned on any crime organization.
我想知道为什么偏偏是他们
I want to know why the Albanians.
他们有菲斯克什么把柄
What did they have on Fisk?
-别管了  -那不行
- Just, uh... let this go. - No, I can't do that.
菲斯克在外面  就会有无辜者死亡
Fisk stays out, innocent people die.
我什么都不知道
I don't know shit.
迈克尔  你可以帮我
Michael, you can help me.
-不行  -拜托了
- No. - Come on.
你会害死我的
You're gonna get me killed.
带他走  我不认识他
Get this guy away from me! I don't know him!
带他走  带他走
Get him away! Get him away!
-够了  -...被犯人袭击
- That's enough! - Assault by an inmate...
我什么都没说
I said nothing.
以我母亲起誓  起誓
On my mother! My mother!
先生
Sir?
没事  误会一场
It's all right. It's just a misunderstanding.
尼尔森先生  你该去找护士看看
Mr. Nelson, you need to get checked out by the nurse.
没事  我没事
It's fine. I'm fine.
那你把这话写在事件报告上吧
Then you can say that on an incident report.
以免我们担责  你得签字才能离开
Liability reasons. Can't let you leave until you sign one.
那好吧
Yeah, all right.
跟我来
Follow me.
他就在这里
He's right in there.
你们好
Hi, boys.
我带来了衣服  漱口水  还有剩菜
I brought clothes, mouthwash, and some leftover chole.
谢谢
Thanks.
真抱歉  这一周都会这样
Hey, I'm sorry. It's gonna be like this all week.
保证你会吃东西  你脸颊都瘪了
You promise me you'll eat? Your face looks thin.
好吧  我会吃的
Fine. Okay, I'll eat.
我爱你
I love you.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
"我们"  萨米也来了
What "we"? Is Sami here?
他在车里  拿手机杀外星人呢
He's in the car, killing aliens on my phone.
我很想见他  带他上来
I'd love to see him. Bring him up.
你在工作  我不想迟到
You're working, and I don't want to be late.
迟到  做什么
Late? Late for what?
去我姐姐家
Late for my sister's.
萨米要去那里住几天
Sami is gonna stay there for a couple of days.
萨米有床了
Sami has a bed.
但他在上面睡不安稳
One that he can't sleep in.
什么意思  怎么了
What do you mean? What's going on?
他整晚不睡  等你回家
He stays up all night, waiting for you to come home.
他看了新闻
He's been watching the news.
他担心你会出事
He's... He's scared something is going to happen to you.
看看我  我没事
Look at me. I'm fine.
是吗
Are you?
因为萨米可不是唯一担心的人
'Cause Sami isn't the only one who's scared.
让他去奈芙家住吧  忘记这些事
Let him stay with Nav and the kids. Get his mind off all of this.
不行
No.
等我回家就跟他谈
I'll talk to him when I come home.
听着  我不会出事的
Look... nothing bad is gonna happen to me.
我去了医院
I was at the hospital.
我跟其他等在急诊室外的家属谈了
I talked to the other spouses waiting outside the ER.
那些探员也都以为
None of those agents thought anything bad
他们不会出事
was going to happen to them, either.
我清楚这次晋升多么重要
I know how much this promotion means,
-但也不值得...  -我们回头再谈吧
- but nothing is worth-- - We can talk about this later.
萨米要去我姐姐家
Sami is going to my sister's.
你一定要吃东西
Make sure you eat.
面墙站好
Face the wall.
快点  转身
Let's go. Turn around.
面墙站好
Against the wall.
快点  额头抵墙  快点  先生们
Now. Foreheads to the wall. Let's go, gentlemen.
腿伸开
Spread your legs.
-在这儿等着  护士就过来  -谢谢
- Wait in here. Nurse should be by. - Thanks.
盖斯多夫
Gelsdorf...
红狮
您好
Yes.
我知道你说要周五早上才能见我
I know you said you couldn't meet until Friday morning,
但我有发现
but I found something.
我觉得等不到那时了
I don't think it can wait till then.
是的  当然  不做记录
Yes, absolutely. Off the record.
不  必须是在联邦存款保险公司工作的人能帮我
No, only somebody who works at the FDIC can help me.
真的
You will?
太感谢了  明天就行
Thank you so much. No... Yeah, tomorrow is perfect.
太好了
Great.
我觉得我查明
I think I figured out how
菲斯克是如何规避联调局的资产冻结了
Fisk has been skirting the FBI asset freeze.
你多久没睡了
When's the last time you slept?
他在通过万科融资
He's been funneling his money through Vancorp,
那是拥有酒店的空壳公司
which is the shell corporation that owns the hotel,
他还把资金放在离岸公司
and he's keeping it in an offshore firm
红狮国家银行里
named Red Lion National Bank.
-凯伦  -这是冒烟枪[铁证]了
- Karen-- - That's the smoking gun.
就算没冒烟  也是热的
If it's not smoking, it's at least kinda warmish.
我不是来谈菲斯克的
I didn't come to talk about Fisk.
什么事
What?
马特吗
It's Matt?
他们找到尸体了
They found a body?
我保证过我再不会为马特向你撒谎了
I promised I would never lie for Matt again. Not to you.
不  你得...
No, you have to just...
你得直接告诉我
You need to just tell me.
马特还活着
Matt's alive.
马特
Matt!
马特  你在哪
Matt, where the hell are you?
他不在这儿  我问过
He's not here. I called.
还问了走廊那边的芙兰是否看到人来转悠
Even asked Fran down the hall if she saw anyone poking around.
她肯定会知道  她可爱多管闲事了
She would know. She pokes.
为什么  他为什么要让我们以为他死了
Why? Why would he let us think that he was dead?
我看到的不是马特  凯伦
It wasn't Matt that I saw, Karen.
并不真是
I mean, not really.
是马特
It was Matt.
一米七七的他  但是
All five feet, ten inches of him, but...
他跟我说话的样子
the way that he spoke to me...
有什么不对劲
something was missing.
这不算新鲜了
Well, that's nothing new.
马特总是有点不对劲
There's always something missing with Matt.
我以前还以为
I used to think that it was...
那是忙碌  心不在焉的律师马特
it was busy lawyer, distracted Matt.
后来我以为是扛着全世界重量的马特
Then I thought it was weight-of-the-world-on-his-shoulders Matt.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
马特就这样
It's just Matt.
但也不是那样的
But it wasn't any of those.
我觉得他有一部分埋在了中城圈地下
I think a part of him was buried under Midland Circle.
我不知道他是否会回来
I don't know if he's coming back.
还保证说不再骗我们了呢
So much for him promising he'd stop lying to us.
让我们以为他死了
Letting us think he was dead.
弥天大谎
A whopper.
我觉得马特已经做出选择了
I think Matt's made his choice.
没给我们留下什么余地了
It doesn't really leave any room for either of us.
是啊
No.
我想也是
I guess it doesn't.
那我可不要坐在这里
Well, I am not going to sit here
等着马特清醒过来
and wait for Matt to come to his senses.
菲斯克出来了  得有人阻止他
Fisk is out, and he has to be stopped.
芙兰错了
Fran was wrong.
看来她也有没看到的
I guess she didn't poke hard enough.
抱歉让你久等
Sorry again for the wait.
但好消息  你没脱臼
But, good news, it's not dislocated.
太好了  我可以走了吗
Great. So I can go?
快好了
Almost done.
老实说  这手续就是浪费时间
Honestly, this paper work is a waste of time.
最终也就是归到档案里
It just ends up in a file somewhere.
我现在要检查你的瞳孔
I am now going to check your pupils
确保你没有脑震荡
to make sure you're not concussed.
-抬头看一下  -别
- Just look up for a minute. - No, just...
拿文件给我签吧
Give me the paper work, please.
好  我放你走
Okay. Let's get you out of here.
我忘了说
I forgot to mention...
如果你接下来几天里觉得头疼
if you come down with any headaches the next couple of days,
务必...
make sure that you...
拜托
Come on.
该死
God damn it.
你不是富兰克林·尼尔森
You're not Franklin Nelson.
菲斯克
Fisk.
真是令人赞叹
It's quite something to see.
作为一个瞎子
For a blind man,
你的反应能力惊人  默多克先生
you have very impressive reflexes, Mr. Murdock.
我被注射了什么
What was I injected with?
记得我们上次说话的时候吗
Do you remember the last time that we spoke?
你说你只要一封信
You said that, for the cost of postage,
就能阻止我
you could prevent my reunion
跟唯一让我的生命有意义的人团聚
with the only person who gives my life meaning.
唯一我爱的人
The only person that I love.
我本会让过去过去的
And I would've let bygones be bygones.
但你不仅威胁了我
But you didn't just threaten me...
你还威胁了凡妮莎
you threatened Vanessa.
这是我不能原谅的
And that is something that I cannot forgive.
仔细听好了
Listen to me very carefully.
那是他吗
Is that him?
他去哪了
Where'd he go?
过来  来  把我放出去
Come here. Come on. Let me outta here.
你去哪  回来
Where you going? Hey, come back.
回来
Come back, man.
跪在地上
On the ground!
等等  我被袭击了
Hold on. I was attacked.
马上跪在地上
Get on the ground now!
我被袭击了  我需要帮助
I was attacked. I need help.
-手放在脑后  -好
- Put your hands behind your head. - Okay.
我们找到他了
All right, we got him.
我们会解决他的
We'll take care of him.
好样的  哥们  拿他的钥匙  快点
Hey, nice job, homes. Grab his keys, quick.
33号警情  33号警情
Code 33, code 33...
现在施行封锁
Lockdown is now in effect.
33号警情  33号警情
Code 33, code 33...
现在施行封锁
Lockdown is now in effect.
点火吧  维克
Light it up, Vic!
33号警情  33号警情
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
现在施行封锁
Lockdown is now in effect.
33号警情  33号警情
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
现在施行封锁
Lockdown is now in effect.
菲斯克会背叛所有人
Fisk betrays everyone!
他也会背叛你的  菲斯克会背叛你的
He will turn on you. Fisk will turn on you, too.
你是谁  菲斯克为什么要你死
Who are you? And why does Fisk want you dead?
等等
Hey, wait...
那是什么  阿尔巴尼亚语吗
What is that? Albanian?
-你是维克吗  -你就不该来
- Are you Vic? - You're an idiot coming here.
菲斯克仍控制着半数预警和囚犯
Fisk still controls half the guards and prisoners.
是啊  但没控制阿尔巴尼亚帮
Yeah, but not... not the Albanians.
因为菲斯克把你们的人卖给了联调局
Not since Fisk ratted your people out to the FBI.
关你什么事
What's it to you?
菲斯克像恨你们一样恨我
Fisk hates me as much as he hates you people.
是我参与把他关了起来  我想再做到一次
I helped get him locked up. And I'm gonna do it again.
不  我觉得你会死在这里
Nah, I think you're gonna die in here.
菲斯克为什么背叛你们的人
Why did Fisk flip on your people?
无所谓
It doesn't matter.
但足以让你想杀他了
It matters enough that you're desperate to kill him.
在这里没成功  在外面又试了一次
You missed him in here, and then you tried again on the outside.
这可是相当严重的指控
That is a very serious allegation.
而且说错了
And wrong.
我们并没试图在这里杀他
We never tried to hit him... in here.
菲斯克在举重室里被捅了
Fisk was shanked in the weight room.
-不是我们干的  -是吗  那是谁
- Not by us. - Oh, yeah? If not you, then who?
如果我成功了  菲斯克又会回来
Listen, if I succeed, Fisk ends up right back here
跟你和你们的人关在一起
with you and your men.
之后  你想怎么处理他就随你了
And after that, you can do with him whatever you please.
是菲斯克捅了菲斯克
Fisk shanked Fisk.
他贿赂了个判终身的捅他
He bribed some lifer to stab him.
他设的计
He set the whole thing up?
那人捅他到足以骗过联调局的程度
The guy sliced him up just good enough to convince the feds.
当然了
Of course.
这个人  判了终身
This guy, he's a lifer?
如果他受了贿赂  那他还活着
If he was bribed, does that mean he's still alive?
比那还好  放走了
Better than alive. Free.
放了  他怎么会没被关禁闭
Free? How is he not in solitary?
菲斯克找人做了假记录  放走了他
Fisk got someone to cook the books and let him out.
好  狱警要来了
Okay, there are guards coming.
告诉我那人的名字
Give me the lifer's name.
他是菲斯克设计了这一切的唯一证据
He's the only proof we have that Fisk set this whole thing up.
-那又如何  -如果我能找到他
- So what? - So if I can get to him, I can--
-你连站都站不稳  -维克  拜托
- You can barely get to your feet. - Vic, please.
你想攻击菲斯克  但没成功
You took a shot at Fisk, and you missed.
我不会失手
I won't.
只有你能帮我出去
Not if you can get me out of here.
33号警情  33号警情
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
现在施行封锁
Lockdown is now in effect.
把那个狱警拖进来
Drag that guard in here.
33号警情  33号警情
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
车队袭击时我们损失了人
Blood was lost during the motorcade attack.
我年轻的亲戚
My baby cousin's blood.
找到那个捅了菲斯克的犯人  兑现你的承诺
Find the inmate who shanked Fisk. Make good on your word.
否则我们会去找你的
Or we'll come find ya.
他叫什么
His name?
贾斯珀·伊万斯
Jasper Evans.
带他出去
Get him outta here.
等等  等一下
Wait, hold on a second.
这里有两个狱警
There's two guards.
走
Okay, now.
-这边  -不  这边有出口
- This way. - No. There's an exit this way.
那边有两个狱警  相信我
There are two guards. Trust me, please.
现在施行封锁
Lockdown is now in effect.
我们得走左边这扇门  走
We need to go through this door on the left. Here.
锁了
It's locked.
你左上兜有把钥匙
There's a key in your top left pocket.
去出口  另一边
Toward the exit! The other way!
快点
Hurry.
他在那里
There he is!
快上
Move! Now!
抓他  走
Get him! Go!
33号警情  33号警情
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
另一边  另一边
The other way. The other way.
慢点  谢谢  谢谢
Slow down. Thank you. Thank you.
犯人  跪下
Inmate! On your knees!
现在施行封锁
Lockdown is now in effect.
-我看不到了  -左边
- I can't see. - Left. Left.
右转  急转
Now take a right. Sharp right.
这里有平民  带他出去  快走
I got a civilian here! Get him out. Go.
快走
Go! Go!
开门  开大门
Open the gate! Open the gate!
开门
Open the gate!
开车  开车
Drive. Drive.
开车
Drive.
老实说
If I'm being honest,
我可没想到会是这样
that's not the way I thought this was gonna go.
谁拿叉勺吃汉堡啊
Who eats a burger with a spork?
-特别探员波因德克斯特  -长官
- Special Agent Poindexter. - Ma'am.
这位是职业责任办公室的温恩特工督察
This is Supervisory Special Agent Winn with OPR.
波因德克斯特
Poindexter.
你去喝杯咖啡吧
Why don't you go grab a cup of coffee?
是  长官
Yes, sir.
德克斯
Dex.
-别紧张  -紧张什么啊
- Don't sweat this. - Sweat what, exactly?
职业责任办公室要跟菲斯克单独问话
OPR wants a private interview with Fisk.
而我是唯一被要求离开的人
And I'm the only one asked to leave the room.
我不应该告诉你
It would be inappropriate of me to tell you
职业责任办公室
that the Office of Professional Responsibility
已发起了针对车队袭击事件的内部调查
has launched an internal investigation into the motorcade attack.
而且我还不应该告诉你
It would also be inappropriate of me to tell you
你的正式报告
that there was a slight discrepancy
跟枪击的鉴证分析
between your official report
稍有不吻合之处
and the forensic analysis of the shooting.
是啊  你是不应该告诉我这些
Yeah, it would be inappropriate for you to tell me all this.
因为你  我妻子还有丈夫
Because of you, my wife still has her husband...
我儿子还有父亲
and my son still has his father.
警探
Detective!
你来做什么  这次活动仅限工会成员
The hell are you doing here? This is a union-only function.
知道我喜欢我们之间的哪一点吗
You know what I love about our dynamic?
我们从不客套
We skip the pleasantries.
不说你好  最近如何  直接说正事
No hellos. No how-you-beens. Straight to business.
我这就要"正式"地
I'm about to get to the business of
把你拽出去了
dragging your ass up outta here.
如果不是要事我也不会来打扰
I wouldn't have intruded if it wasn't important.
我猜猜  你要我帮忙
Let me guess. You need a favor.
瞧
See?
你跟别人也有这样的默契吗
Do you have this kind of shorthand with anyone else?
威尔逊·菲斯克
Wilson Fisk.
他舒适的新境遇
His cushy new situation
就是一记联邦资助的大耳光
is a federally-funded slap in the face
扇在这房间里每一位警察的脸上
to every officer in this room.
可不是
No shit.
但我不知道这跟你
Not sure what that has to do
跑来闯派对有什么关系
with you crashing this party, though.
我想说几句话  表达一下同仇敌忾的情绪
I want to say a few words, express my solidarity.
如果你能替我介绍就更好了
And it would play better if you gave me the floor.
就说几句话
Just to say a few things.
这周很漫长  福吉  好吗
It's been a long week, Foggy, okay?
你的讲话只会是伤口撒盐
And you talking is only gonna drag it out.
你该走了
Now, it's time to go.
要么我铐你  要么你自己走
In handcuffs or on your own.
不用多说了
Say no more.
布莱特  你好吗
Hey, Brett, how's it going?
打扰一下  各位尊敬的警官
Excuse me, esteemed constables.
各位  请容我...
Guys, could I have--
律师  我想亲自感谢你
Hey, Counselor, I personally wanna thank you
凭咬文嚼字把我的纵火犯放出监狱
for springing my arson perp out of jail on a technicality.
拜托  那是有减刑情节的
Come on. There were mitigating circumstances,
你很清楚  警官
and you know it, Officer.
他的大楼不符合标准
His building was not up to code.
我让你见识一下你的减刑情节该插哪吧
Let me show you where to stick your mitigating circumstances.
各位
People, look, um...
尼尔森还行  他帮忙把菲斯克关了起来
Nelson's all right. He helped the city put Fisk behind bars.
让他说吧
Give him a minute.
就一分钟
One minute.
警官们  我不想让你们失望
Officers, I don't mean to disappoint.
但我不是单纯来谈威尔逊·菲斯克的
But I'm not here to talk only about Wilson Fisk.
人人都在谈论他
With his name on everyone's lips,
一个警察杀手不该获得如此的关注
he's getting far more publicity than any cop killer deserves.
他的名字应该被埋起来
His name deserves to be buried...
跟你们牺牲的弟兄一样  埋在黄土之下
buried in the same hard earth where he put your fallen brothers.
我是来谈布雷克·陶瓦的
I'm here to talk about Blake Tower...
我们尊敬的地检官
our honorable district attorney.
此人
Here's a man
跟你们一样  被委以保护城市安全的重任
charged with ensuring the safety of this city, just as you are.
然而  他袖手旁观
And yet, he stands idly by
让联调局把那个怪物带出监狱
while the feds whisk that monster out of prison
送进奢侈的舒适中
and into the warm lap of luxury.
一个比我聪明的人...
Someone smarter than me--
律师  这要求可不高  是吧
Hey, counselor, that's a pretty freakin' low bar, isn't it?
曾说  "邪恶若想胜利
That man said, "The only thing necessary for the triumph of evil
只需要好人无所作为"
is for good men to do nothing."
布雷克·陶瓦是个好人  他无所作为
Blake Tower is a good man doing nothing.
所以
Which is why
我要临时参选地检官
I'm running my own write-in campaign for district attorney,
赶走布雷克·陶瓦
to oust Blake Tower
把威尔逊·菲斯克关进第八修正案允许范围内
and to put Wilson Fisk into the deepest prison hole allowable
最深的监狱
under the Eighth Amendment.
我非常希望
And I would love nothing more than to do that
能够得到诸位  和你们工会的支持
with the endorsement of each of you and your illustrious union.
我在哪签字
All right, where do I sign up?
小宝贝  小宝贝
Hey, baby. Hey, baby.
你好啊
Hey, what's up, yo?
看那小矮子
Look at shorty comin'.
留个名字吧
Let me get your name.
-我们绕着走吧  -我们玩玩嘛
- Let's go around. - What we getting into?
你们好啊  留个名字吧
What's up, y'all? Let me get your names.
来吗  一起玩玩嘛
Come on! What we getting into tonight?
去哪啊  美女  我们整晚有空
Where you going, Ma? We got all night!
那小妞走过来了  哥们
See, that ass is walking away, bro.
给你了  哥们  归你了
Yo, that's all you, bro. That's all you, bro.
这可是位淑女呢
Now, this is a real lady.
过来  你来打招呼的吗
Come here. You coming to say hi?
我们今晚可以好好玩玩  喜欢玩吗
We could have some fun tonight. Yeah, you like fun?
给我闪开
Get out of my way.
你挺横  跟我们玩玩吧
You got bite. Come on, play with us.
我们玩个游戏吧
Let's play a game.
你想玩什么  我扮演害怕小姑娘的游戏吗
What do you wanna play? The one where I play scared little girl?
因为你似乎喜欢吓唬女孩子
'Cause it seems you like scaring girls.
没事的  我们就是闹闹
It's all good. We was just having fun.
那我们玩吧  谁先来  你还是我
Let's have fun. Huh? Who goes first? You? Me?
女士  我们没有恶意
Lady, we were just being friendly.
那我也是好意提醒你
Then this is just a friendly reminder
这样的游戏能害你送命
that games like that can get your head blown off.
你怎么还不走
Why are you still here?
家里有事吗
Trouble at home?
没有
Um, no, I...
其实  那不关我的事
Actually, that's none of my business.
不是  我是需要点帮助  建议
No, no. Um... I could use some help, advice.
我不知道
I don't know.
你以前也遭遇过袭击吧
You've taken fire before, right?
够多次了
Enough.
你当时有孩子吗
You have kids at the time?
你儿子无法接受枪击的事吗
Your boy having trouble with the shooting?
嗯
Yeah.
他睡不着  看新闻
Yeah, he's, uh, not sleeping, you know... watching the news.
什么的
Stuff like that.
我觉得最好的办法就是像男人那样直接跟他谈
I mean, I think the best thing to do is talk to him like a man.
告诉他我的工作很危险  但我...
Tell him that the job I do is dangerous, but I--
我建议  别
My advice... don't.
我对我女儿那么做了
I tried that with my daughter.
把她吓坏了
It freaked her out so bad,
她早上都不让我离家
she wouldn't let me leave the house in the morning.
她躺在门口哭
She lay across the door and cried
直到我不得不请了假
until I called in and took the day.
把你儿子当做线人
Treat your son like a CI.
把我的孩子当成我的告密人
Make my kid my snitch?
告密人生活在他们无法掌控的世界里
Snitch lives in a scary world they don't control,
他们依赖你的保护
and they depend on you to keep 'em safe.
耳熟吗
Sound familiar?
嗯  但对我儿子撒谎
Yeah, but lying to my son...
我爸爸是个卡车司机
My dad was a trucker.
他主要拉化学物罐车
He mostly hauled chemical tankers.
他有时会把车开回家过夜
He'd bring 'em to the house overnight
然后再出发
before heading out sometimes.
我会做噩梦  想着可能发生什么坏事
And I'd have nightmares, thinking about what could happen.
但我爸知道后
But when my dad found out,
他带我看了车后面的钻石状贴花纸
he showed me a diamond-shaped decal on the back
五颜六色还有数字
with the colors and numbers.
他说  数字代表了危险程度
He told me the numbers tell you how high the level of danger is.
他只拉四级的最安全物质
He only hauled level four, safest stuff.
我一知道  就不觉得很可怕了
Once I knew that, it didn't seem so scary anymore.
-四级是最致命的  -但我不知道
- Level four is the most lethal code. - But I didn't know that.
我也不会担心
And I didn't worry
他每天早晨拉着带轮子的火炸弹出发
when he drove off every morning in a rolling fire bomb.
保护我们的谎言值得撒
The lies that keep us safe are the ones worth telling.
来吗
Coming?
佩吉小姐  你怎么来了
Ms. Page? What are you doing here?
我知道我们约的是明天
I know we had an appointment for tomorrow,
但我要谈的事等不到那时了
but what we have to talk about can't wait till then.
这是我家
This is my home.
-我的家人在楼上  -我知道  对不起
- My family is upstairs. - I know. I'm sorry.
我愿意跟你说话你就算走运了
You're lucky I'm willing to talk to you, period.
如果我在联邦存款保险公司的老板知道我...
If my bosses at the FDIC found out I was talking--
红狮国家银行
Red Lion National Bank.
你怎么知道我的地址的
And how the hell did you get my address?
-是埃里森...  -不是
- Did Ellison put you up-- - No.
埃里森不知道我来了
Ellison doesn't know that I'm here.
他也不知道我联系了你
He doesn't know that I reached out to you.
我知道这不好
I know that looks bad--
如果你知道  你就不会来了
And if you did, you wouldn't be standing here.
你越早告诉我红狮的事  我就能越早走
The sooner you tell me about Red Lion, the sooner I go.
威尔逊·菲斯克在用那个银行洗钱
Wilson Fisk is laundering his money through that bank.
上百万呢
We're talking millions of dollars.
-亲爱的  是谁啊  -工作上的人
- Honey, who's at the door? - Someone from work.
联邦存款保险公司肯定监控了相关银行...
The FDIC has to be monitoring a bank involved--
我没什么可说的了
We're done here.
别  我...
No, I just...
我需要证据
I need proof.
给我一个银行的联络人
Give me a contact at the bank.
我早上会联系埃里森的
I'll be having words with Ellison in the morning.
告诉我个名字  你就再不会见到我了
Give me a name, you will never see me again.
亲爱的  怎么回事
Honey, what's going on?
只有一个名字值得一查
There's only one name worth checking into, and...
你不可能从他嘴里问出什么来
good luck squeezing anything out of him.
谁
Who?
菲利克斯·曼宁
Felix Manning.
谢谢
Thank you.
你给我走远点就是谢我了
Thank me by getting the hell off my property.
抱歉
Sorry.
我以为你今天都不用来了
I thought you were relieved for the day.
-大家都走了吗  -嗯
- Is everyone gone? - Yeah.
好  那好
Good. Yeah, that's good.
你下楼去喝杯咖啡吧
Why don't you go downstairs, grab a cup of coffee?
我请客
My treat.
好
Yeah.
好主意
That's a good idea.
我...
I'll just...
嗯
Yeah.
你记得他们几个吗
Do you remember these men?
他们是袭击车队的阿尔巴尼亚帮
They were among the Albanians who attacked the motorcade.
-你看到他们死了吗  -是的
- Did you see these men die? - Yes, I did.
你看到是谁打死了他们吗
And did you see who shot them?
当时只剩一个联调局探员还活着了
There was only one FBI agent left standing.
特别探员波因德克斯特
Special Agent Poindexter.
他枪击他们的时刻
The moment he shot them,
你可以描述下你的所见以做记录吗
can you describe, for the record, what you saw?
他们有武器
They were armed.
特别探员波因德克斯特给了他们投降的机会
Special Agent Poindexter gave them a chance to surrender,
但他们却举起武器想打他
but then their weapons came up to shoot him.
他为自卫杀了他俩
He killed them both in self-defense.
谢谢你配合  菲斯克先生
Thank you for your time, Mr. Fisk.
-你想玩什么  -玩
- What's your game? - Game?
我不需要你帮我忙  犯人
I don't need any favors from you, convict.
帮忙  不
Favors, no.
但同情
But sympathy...
报纸  抗议
Papers, protests...
嘲讽
the mockery.
我能承担这份羞辱的重担  可你呢
I can carry this burden of humiliation, but you?
你是个功勋卓著的联邦探员
You're a dedicated federal agent.
你根本不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
《公报》也不了解
Neither does the Bulletin.
联调局搞砸了菲斯克的转移
媒体把对我的袭击说成了是联调局的大砸锅
The press is labeling the attack on my life as an FBI disaster.
现在  他们要因为你的尽职而调查你
And now they're investigating you for doing your job.
他们因为你的突出而质疑你
They're questioning you for your exceptionalism.
你救了我一命
You saved my life!
还有好联邦探员的命
And the lives of honorable federal agents.
他们报道那个了吗
Did they report that?
没有
No.
他们只是中伤
Instead, they vilify...
贬低了你的英勇行为
and demean your act of courage.
世界变了
The world is changing.
真正的英雄被嘲笑贬低
The real heroes are ridiculed and dismissed.
为此  我表示同情
And for that, I offer my sympathy.
我们在哪
Where are we?
哪...
Where...
等等
Wait...
等等  停车
Hold up. Stop the car.
没事的  我送你回家
No problem. We'll get you home.
你是谁
Who are you?
不不不
No, no, no. No.